{Wise man Racine moves throughout the auditorium
ministering prayer in the name of Jesus Christ!
And the power of God is released to the saints,
people are receiving deliverance
the power of the Holy Spirit.
The name Jesus Christ has power indeed.
But to only those who are committed to the power of God.
As wise man Racine ministers to
the people he encounters this man.
And the evil spirit that was responsible
to his problems is exposed
Lets watch what happens next.}
(In the mighty name of Jesus Christ,
Holy Ghost fire all over your body in the name of Jesus
Who are you?)
I have told you before
(Who are you?)
I have told you, you cant him from me.
(Who are you? speak to me In the name of Jesus!)
I am the spirit from the family.
(How do you operate as the spirit from his family?)
I have stopped many of them,
he is the last man standing
(How did you stop them?)
Two of his uncles were men of God,
I made them to be useless.
(How?)
They are even dead
Look at him, he was working for me.
(He was working for you?)
And now he says he want to serve God.
He is a great man, but i have messed him up.
I have frustrated his ministry.
(How have you frustrated his ministry?)
You know it
(Explain, how?)
You want to know?
He will gather the crowd, he will pray for people;
He will heal many.
They will go and give testimony somewhere else.
His church will go down,
he will struggle and he will go down.
I have frustrated him, I want him to leave the ministry
to serve me.
(How do you operate in the life of this man?)
How I operate?
I made him to be angry,
I sent one of my demons of anger,
When I frustrate him he become angry,
and when he become angry, he gets discouraged.
And he doesnt work for his master any more.
(So you entered him through anger?)
Yes, I entered him, I sent the spirit of anger in him.
You cant stop me,
because I have stayed for too long.
He will not become what that Man wants him to be.
(Which Man?)
The Man up there.
(Which Man??)
Oh You don't know him?
(Name him, what is his name?)
We are not authorised to call his name.
(Why? what does that name do to you?)
The name shakes the Kingdom.
(His name shake your kingdom?)
Yes!
(What else have you done to this man?)
I have raised people in the community
and everywhere he goes they look at him as nothing.
He is a fighter, but ?I would not let him.
(A fighter?)
Yes he is a fighter
He loves God, he has sacrificed,
he is the last born in the family.
of six, I have killed the rest of them.
Just him, the last born, he wants to shine.
He is even the only one that tried to get married.
Look at this small boy, he cannot become...
(what have you done to his family?)
His family?
Yes!
All his family- fighting, quarreling.
I am at the verge of breaking the marriage.
(Who is this woman?)
Who?
(This woman?)
(Who is she?)
She is one of your members
(You don't know her?)
She is one of your members.
(Madam, you are welcome, who is this man?)
He is my husband.
(What can you say about him?)
He has anger
He gets very angry and it affects
even the people of the church,
(How?)
When he gets a little bit
angry he talks angry to the people,
and some of them leave
the church because of his anger.
Even me, he threatens me.
(He threatens you?)
Yes, he tells me am the witch,
I am the one making people to leave the church.
He tells me he doesnt want to hear my voice.
Sometimes he doesn't want me to minister
He tells me that I am the witch,
every time he says I am the witch.
(Madam, it is not him but that spirit.)
(Come here, how do you explain;
how did you enter this man again?)
How did I manage to enter him?
(Yes)
When he was a young boy.
I saw a light and when we was living with one of the aunties,
The aunt was a prostitute
and when the mother died, the aunt took him.
And there we took advantage of the light,
and when he was living with the aunt
who was doing prostitution.
We took advantage and we entered him.
Then we knew, he would come to deliver the family,
Now, we will stop him because he came here,
because he has tried and cannot,
and now you are asking me, "Who am I?"
Do you know who I am?
(Who are you?)
You want to know me?
Look at me, I am the great one.
(The great one?)
Yes!
(What do you mean by the great one?)
You want to know?
The great one,
I have worked in that family and their family,
nobody is rising.
I have made them to be nothing.
He is coming to your God, and he is giving all.
He has abandoned us
I said that if he continues serving that God, I will kill him.
(Listen to me, Jesus Christ is greater than you.
Today in the mighty name of Jesus Christ,
I command you demon to leave this man for ever.
Come out, come out In the name of Jesus!
Out!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ.)
(In Jesus name!
Stand up!
Come here!
Come!
Come sir! come!
How are you?)
Fine sir.
(Is this your wife?)
Yes my wife we came here together.
(Do you remember what you have just said?)
I said she is my wife.
(What happened to you?)
Sir, Its so embarrassing
I am not properly dressed.
(What brought you here?
Listen to me, Jesus Christ
of Nazareth has cast out that demon.
That unclean spirit that was
destroying your life and your destiny.
You are free today in the name of Jesus!)
Amen
Thank you Jesus!
(Madam, that spirit of anger,
that evil spirit. Jesus has cast it out.
He is no longer the same person. )
Amen!
(Don't remind him his past,
his past is over. you are free!)
Thank you sir
(You are free!)
Thank you sir, thank you Jesus!
Emmanuel(God with us!)
Our names, Apostle and prophetess Tobe,
we come from Cameroon.
We are the pastors of Dominion Christian Center.
The problem that brought us to SCOAN
were, setback, depression and oppression
in our lives, in the ministry and even in our family.
By the grace of God,
I have been a pastor for more that 10 years.
However, things have not been going well
We would have great programs,
thousands of people would gather
They would come to church but in the space of one month,
they are gone.
We would pray for people healing and deliverance,
they would go and give testimony somewhere else.
The same people would not come to church anymore.
This thing has been for more than 10 years.
As a man of God, I have been praying and fasting.
We put our hand together and say
"we need to pray, this thing what is happening?"
Why is our lives like this?
Look at this one? we prayed for them
What is happening to us?
We knew there was something more
than us that we didn't understand.
My wife and I agreed to come because
I discovered that every time we tried to come to SCOAN
there would always be one problem
or the other or one misunderstanding.
Before we knew it the journey is postponed.
But when this year began we said, well, we are not going
to sit down and take up with the ministry like that.
We need to come to SCOAN
Because we believed that God has to say something
concerning our situation.
When we came here last week Sunday,
we were privileged to be inside the church.
We sat down, just under the gallery in the church
And when prayer was going on
after the praises and worship,
when the wise men came up and they
were praying and ministering deliverance.
wise man Racine came to the raw where i was,
where he was praying
Before he even came I was just normal,
and there was a kind of weight upon me.
I was just being so heavy.
When he came, he laid his hand on me and
I felt a burning sensation in my body.
And there was a reaction, I felt something left me.
And right there, i knew something was wrong with me
When the prayer was going on and the delivarance
I discovered that there was an evil spirit from
my family that had taken hold
not only in my life but it had started
with others of my family members.
It has held me for all this years
I discovered that the evil spirit
even said that two of my uncles,
It had stopped them and killed them.
That they will not fulfill their ministry
When I thought about it, I remebered, it is true
two of my uncles were pastors
as I grew up as a young man, they loved the lord
They were doing wonders but they were nothing
even till their death they were nothing
I never understood what was happening
When my mother died I was taken to
my aunt in one of the cites in Cameroon
and she was a prostitute.
The spirit was saying that it has taken advantage of me
I never knew.
I discovered that when I was
in the city of Duala as a young man,
living with my aunt,
whenever she had business we would go out for a stroll,
We would be walking at 12 midnight
we would still be walking as a
young man with some evil bad boys.
Guys that were smoking
I even discovered that,
I even got to piece one of my ear
and there was ear ring there.
{From that time when you were growing up with your aunt
what were the other things that you passed through, on your way to
on the way to becoming here at the SCOAN.}
When I was with my aunt,
since she was doing the business of prostitution
I was just living a life that was not pleasing to God
And in that time I became born again thereafter.
I loved the Lord, I was serving the Lord, I was faithful
and I recieved a call to serve the Lord
And I discovered that, when I was with my aunt
Something happened because
this spirit had haunted my family
We are six children and all are dead,
I am the last born
As a young man, when they saw that
people were dying they took us
My aunt took us to a shrine where
Incisions were made on our bodies.
They said that they wanted to protect
us from an evil spirit
so that we would not die
They cut marks on my legs and hands and took
the blood and put on a black stone.
I was so innocent I never knew what was happening,
I thought it was protection.
And then we went
As I was still a christian growing in the Lord,
I received the call of God
and I was doing the work of God
but things were not going well.
things were not moving
Great crusades people would gather,
miracles but not in my life.
nothing to show forth
People would say, great man of God,
You are Wonder full
But when you look at me, you look at
every thing around, you may ask, "where is the wonder?"
They are taking the church from one court to the another.
At one time I wondered, "what is this problem?"
I told my life, "Its not by force, If I am
not a pastor, I can be a christian."
The spirit was telling me, leave dont do this work
You can see it is not working
It came to a point i said to myself, It is not by force"
I said that I just wasnt to be a normal christian
Every time, I said that I was not a pastor
that thing became very heavy on me
My wife was saying, "No you need to pray more."
I knew I was no longer interested with
the ministry because of what I saw.
The kind of challenges i was having, were not normal.
And from that moment we agreed to come to SCOAN
for deliverance
{Hallelujah, sir can you tell us how has
this spirit affected your family,
your relationship with your wife and your marriage?}
That spirit has actually affected my relationship
because I discovered my uncles who
were pastors were married to two wives
As a young man growing I wondered,
How can a pastor have two wives
I discovered that the urge of getting
another woman was really strong
It was just 99.1 percent
Like i just need to get another wife
I had no feelings for my wife
I mean to say that for the 10 years that we have been married,
this is the eleventh year
Things have not been moving, we have no child
And I know that that spirit is responsible for my childlessness.
I thank God because,
the kind of feelings i have for my wife was
not that kind of feeling for husband and wife.
We would hide it, when we come outside,
"Praise the lord! Hallelujah! Glory to God!
But when we go back to the house, it would be, 'Tom and Jerry'
We were quarreling for nothing
We were just quarreling and this has affected my ministry.
It has affected my life as a man of God.
{Glory be to God, so you are here today and that is
what brought you to the SCOAN
Now tell us since your delivarance in the name of Jesus Christ, how has your life been?}
Praise theLord!
If you are happy with the testimony, Praise the Lord!
You dont know what I have gone through
If you knew what I have gone through,
you will jump and say hallelujah with me.
Praise the Lord
Before I came here, you look at the man
"Oh wonderful man of God- handsome, great
but you dont know what was wrong with me
You dont know what was killing me within
I never knew how to get rid of it
I have fasted, I have prayed in my own capacity
But when I came here since the prayer of the wise man
my life, the urge of leaving the ministry,
the urge of going out of the ministry
I don't have it anymore
There is a burning passion, sensention to serve God upon me
{Lets put our hands together for Jesus!
My wife can testify because
in our relationship was not working,
now I feel a married man.
I feeli like a father
I feel i have a companion by my side
I feel there is somebody by my side
Its just like we have just entered into a new marriage
I know it is a new marriage after my deliverance,
I know it is a new ministry after my deliverance,
I know I am a new person after my deliverance,
Hallelujah!
I want to say this,
I have received more than 80 calls from last week
The whole Cameroon as am talking they are watching me.
Calls have been coming,
man of God we are waiting for you
I thought, "its me?"
Things have just been wonderful because i know this is God.
I want to say this, The Bible says, "Pride goes before a fall."
As a man of God, Prophet TB Joshua said something
God looks at our spirit, the spirit of humility.
I discovered that many of us men of God,
have an attitude or character problem.
I am a man of God, I am anointed,
it is God that called me
I don't need anybody to deliver me, God will deliver me.
But my bible tells me that by a prophet
Israel was preserved
and by a prophet Israel was delivered.
I believe in this dispensation, God has sent his servant
Prophet TB Joshua as a prophet for
the deliverance and liberation of Gods people.
I want to advice my fellow ministers,
You will agree with me that graces are given to each and everyone
according to the measure of faith.
You are listening to me and you know
that this situations you are going through.
You have prayed, you have fasted with me.
It is time to identify a higher grace and
trusting God for your deliverance.
Just like I did.
Come out of your pride, collar and title
You might be a bishop, apostle, prophet , an evangelist
I want you to know God is interested in your life,
not your title
If you are carrying your title
and claiming not to be delivered,
Just like me, when I entered the
ministry I wasn't truly been delivered
But now I know there is a new page
in my life, my family and my ministry.
I want to advice you, Trust God
Dont come to the SCOAN just to look at the man of God
the beauty of the place and the people
Come and connect your spirit with the spirit of the man of God.
Iron sharpens iron and I know your life
will never remain the same again
{Glory be to God. Sir we thank God Almighty for your life
and the wonderful thing God has done for you
and your family, and we want to encourage you that
You should make Gods word the standard for your life.
God almighty will continue to give you the mercy and favor you
that you have began to walk in his ministry in the name of Jesus Christ.}
I want to testify one more thing
Before I came here, I had lost my voice for two years,
I had an album and people would say, Oh, it is good!
but nobody was buying it
That spirit has hindered my life.
I discovered that in those days, I was singing,
there was healing and deliverance.
But I found out that my voice is gone
but after my deliverance
I began to wonder, "Is it me?"
I recorded my voice.
My voice now is like a refined voice
When I sing I can hear myself
And I know the Holy Spirit is speaking through me.
I was saying that, If I am given the privilege
I would like to sing one song
For the glory of God,
because what God has done for me,
no amount of money can pay for it.
[Glory
Glory to the lamb
Glory
For you are glorious
and worthy to be praised
The Lamb upon the throne,
And you shall reign
In righteousness for ever
You are the Lamb upon the throne.]
Hallelujah!
Praise the Lord!
Emmanuel,( God with us, Matt 1:23)
People of God, tears of joy is running down my eyes.
We have gone through a lot
and this is the day, time and season.
That the Lord has made for us,
to cross over the bridge
It is our time and our season that the Lord has made.
My name is prophetess Blessing Dora Tabe.
We are pastors of Dominion Christian Center in Cameroon.
We came here because of oppression,
stagnation and difficulties in our ministry
and in our lives; things have not been working.
Since last year; before then,
we have been saying that we will come to SCOAN
but there was no way.
There was no money for use to come.
Sometimes we were wondering, "God! how are we going to do it?"
But I knew in my spirit that one day, we will come here.
Early last year, I had a dream
that Prophet TB Joshua came to our church.
and he was preaching.
While he was preaching, he stopped at
one point and he started prophesying.
Suddenly a python appeared at the corner of the church
and a hand came and killed the python.
He prayed for me two times.
I had been so oppressed in my spirit
I told my husband that this is the time for us to go to SCOAN
at all costs.
Whether there is money or there is
no money we will go there.
Because I had seen this, I prayed with
Prophet TB Joshua, touching the screen.
Whenever he is praying I lay my hands,
I have been praying for ourselves, for the church.
And I knew that one day, God will bring us here.
When we got here, Wiseman Racine
prayed for my husband
and the spirit manifested
Everything that the spirit said was true
Because all along the spirit was using
my husband to accuse me,
that I was the witch in the church;
causing all people to go.
And it was such a burden to me.
Sometimes I would tell him that,
I would leave the church and travel
I would go away for even one year
so that the church will be intact
so that people would not go anymore.
And each time the Spirit of God would
come to me and say, No!
stand , and and see what I would do."
Every time I would tell my husband that this this is more than us,
we have to go for deliverance
Every time I would say, "Let us go and seek the face of the man of God."
I would think of some men of God around us.
but my spirit would not allow me.
I'd Tell him that we would come only to SCOAN
as I had the dream last year.
I said, "no, this is the place that God is sending us.
No matter what, we would go"
And I know that this is the beginning of-our deliverance
and that spirit that used to come to us,
in the dream, when we were sleeping,
There is a snake that comes to us,
at one time I told my husband, a python came to us
as we were sleeping.
and in that dream, you did nothing; and a python came and pass.
I saw that God was protecting us.
Even him, he said that there was a woman
that was coming to his dream to sleep with him.
All those things were hindrances that the spirit
was doing to stop us from going forward
Nothing was moving, no money- Nothing!
The ministry was going up and down.
people were coming and going
and all the blame was on me.
I told my husband that, In the arena of Liberty SCOAN
God is going to visit us
and the truth is going to come out of this matter
I thank the Lord for his deliverance
for our lives,
praise the Lord!
I want to advice the ministers of God,
that,
They should stand, no matter what they see
and serve the Lord because there is a way that
the Lord will show up.
Because 'Jesus is the way the truth and the life.'
God has shown us the way
and He has brought us here to get our total deliverance.
Because our efforts could not do anything
And we saw that we were depreciating,
we were frustrated,
and people were mocking us, deserted
And I want to tell women of God that
are standing by their husbands.
When they see that things are not moving, they should stand
Because i stood.
Even my family members told me,
"what are you doing with that man?"
"He is nothing, leave him.
nothing will work from there"
Even other men of God have rejected us, but I tell you
Men and women of God out there ,
stand and see the salvation of the lord.
If it is not going, come to the arena of liberty.
And you will receive your deliverance in Jesus name.
{We thank God almighty for the wonderful thing
He has done in your life.
And we encourage you that as you continue
to make the word of God the standard for your life.
the best is yet to come!
In Jesus name.}
Amen!